

# NGUYỄN THANH TUẨN ANH

JUNIOR .NET DEVELOPER



Apply experience in coding skills and understanding of the market to become a professional fullstack developer, bringing a lot of value to customers. Thereby helping the Company increase the number of customers and expand the customer base.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

09/2022 - Present

EximBank

**Software Developer** 

- -Build an API system for application development partners
- -Build website systems to serve internal work needs
- -Maintain and participate in the development of available projects.
- -Participate in technical support at major company events

04/2022 - 07/2022

**TMA Solutions** 

Intern

- -Learn knowlege to become fullstack developer.
- -Create project individual to improve skill.

08/2018 - 08/2022

Software engineering

University of Economics and Finance UEF

- -Ability to lead small teams during college.
- -Knowledge current frameworks.



Số điện thoại

0962411810



tuananhnguyenthanh521@gmail.com



Địa chỉ

**Email** 

Quận 10,TPHCM



Ngày sinh

02/03/2000



Giới tính

Nam



# **EDUCATION**

University of Economics and Finance UEF | 08/2018 - 08/2022

SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGY

Graduated



# **SKILLS**

#### Back-end

- C#,.Net core, MVC, WebAPI
- -Restful API, Spring Framework

#### Front end

- -ReactJs, VueJs, NextJs.
- -Html, Css, Js, Tailwindcss.

#### **Other**

- -SQLServer, Mysql, Mongodb
- -Git.
- -SOLID, Agile, Scrum.

#### Office Information Technology

- Proficient in using Word, Excel, Power Point



# Certificate

2022

English B1

© topcv.vn